/* 
 * To change this license header, choose License Headers in Project Properties.
 * To change this template file, choose Tools | Templates
 * and open the template in the editor.
 */

var questions = [{
	"question":"The service will begin ___ five minutes.",
	"option1":"in",
	"option2":"on",
	"option3":"with",
	"option4":"about",
	"answer":"1"
},  {
	"question":"Who is___,Brian or Teddy?",
	"option1":"tallest",
	"option2":"tall",
	"option3":"taller",
	"option4":"the tallest",
	"answer":"3"
},  {
	"question":"Maria___never late for work.",
	"option1":"am",
	"option2":"are",
	"option3":"were",
	"option4":"is",
	"answer":"4"
},  {
	"question":"I have a___cards left to post.",
	"option1":"few",
	"option2":"fewer",
	"option3":"less",
	"option4":"little",
	"answer":"1"
},  {
	"question":"Ms Kibati___ rather not invest that money.",
	"option1":"has to",
	"option2":"could",
	"option3":"would",
	"option4":"must",
	"answer":"3"
},  {
	"question":"Mr Maina requests that someone___the data by fax",
	"option1":"sent",
	"option2":"sends",
	"option3":"send",
	"option4":"to send",
	"answer":"2"
},  {
	"question":"He goes to work_____",
	"option1":"by taxi",
	"option2":"on taxi",
	"option3":"with taxi",
	"option4":"in taxi",
	"answer":"1"
},  {
	"question":"Nothing___done when the boss is away.",
	"option1":"becomes",
	"option2":"gets",
	"option3":"been",
	"option4":"got",
	"answer":"2"
},  {
	"question":"Which one is incorrect?",
	"option1":"clotheful",
	"option2":"clothing",
	"option3":"clothed",
	"option4":"clothe",
	"answer":"1"
},  {
	"question":"I ____ tv yesterday night.",
	"option1":"viewed",
	"option2":"watched",
	"option3":"saw",
	"option4":"looked",
	"answer":"2"
}

];


